<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Rob Cannon</title><link>https://RobCannon.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Rob Cannon</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><copyright>Copyright © 2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://RobCannon.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://RobCannon.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://RobCannon.github.io/about/</guid><description>Attributions # This site depends on the following projects:
Powered by Hugo Based largely on hugo-theme-gruvbox Which heavily uses hugo-mod-json-resume Color scheme based on Gruvbox Code Highlighting by Prism Tabler Icons Simple Icons Legal # The site is licensed under MIT.
All trademarks are the property of their respective owners.</description></item><item><title>Awards/Education/Volunteering</title><link>https://RobCannon.github.io/awards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://RobCannon.github.io/awards/</guid><description>Awards # 2014-2015 Technology and Engineering EMMY Award 2015-12-31 The National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences Pioneering Development of Data Driven Traffic System for Multichannel Environments I was the team lead of the development Crossroad team that won this award.
Education # Computer Science (Bachelor&amp;#39;s Degree) 1983-12-31 - 1986-12-31 Southern Polytechnic State University 3.9/4.0 - High Honors Volunteering # Web Developer 2010-12-31 - 2012-12-31 Lighthouse Family Retreat I developed a web site to track volunteer information and to register families with children with cancer.</description></item><item><title>Experience</title><link>https://RobCannon.github.io/experience/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://RobCannon.github.io/experience/</guid><description>Director of Cloud Services 2019-07-31 - present Equifax Alpharetta, Georgia, United States Leading the engineering team that builds the core infrastructure security blocks to allow Equifax to migrate to the Google Cloud Platform and comply with FedRAMP standards.
Established best practices for managing Google Kubernetes Engine and created Terraform automation that teams can use create clusters that meet high Equifax security standards. Continuing to bring new functionality such as Anthos Service Mesh and Anthos Configuration Manger as part of the Equifax standard for GKE.</description></item><item><title>Skills</title><link>https://RobCannon.github.io/skills/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://RobCannon.github.io/skills/</guid><description>IT Management ()
Strategic Planning, Vendor Management, Audit Compliance, Security Compliance, Business Continuity, Agile Planning, Enterprise Architecture, SDLC, Budgets Public Clouds ()
GCP, AWS, Azure Platform Technologies ()
Kubernetes, Docker, Serverless, Elastic Search, Prometheus Compliance ()
FedRAMP, SOX, PCI Tools ()
Terraform, Packer, PowerShell, Microsoft Office DevOps ()
GitHub Actions, Azure Devops, Jenkins, Continuous Integration Programming Languages ()</description></item></channel></rss>